晚上好 酒保先生
Evening, barkeep.
麻烦给我来点儿含酒精的东西
I would like to purchase some alcohol, please.
你要什么
Uh-huh. What can I get you?
看看我的证件
Well, I'm 26, as you can see.
我已经26岁了
From my license.
祝贺你 你想要什么
Congratulations. What can I get you?
一杯香蕉代基里酒 朋友
A banana daiquiri, my good man.
我叫克丽丝多
I'm Crystal.
你叫什么
What's your name?
你好 克丽丝多 我是加里
Hi, Crystal. I'm Gary.
加里 我本不想令你尴尬的
Gary, I don't want to embarrass you,
但是你是个
But you are just …
你看起来真的太迷人了
You are just a stunning-looking man.
我就知道
I know, right?
谢谢
Ooh! Thanks!
加里 你今晚玩得开心吗
So, Gary, you having a good time tonight?
谢谢关心 克丽丝多
Mm! Thank you for asking, Crystal.
这简直是我过得最棒的一晚
This is, like, the best night ever.
你说我们还能不能让它更棒一些呢
Do you think we could make it any better?
可能吧 我也不清楚
Probably. I don't know.
我是说 你想出去走走吗
I mean, do you want to get out of here?
我 我挺喜欢这里的
Well, I-I kind of like this bar.
我才刚点了这杯代基里酒
And I just ordered this daiquiri.
我是指
I mean…
你想不想和我一起离开这里
Do you want to get out of here with me?
我们这是在说性之类的吗
Are we talking about sex?
我
Well, I, uh …
是的 就是这样
Yeah. I suppose we are.
克丽丝多 我非常乐意跟你做爱
Crystal, I would love to have the sex with you.
好极了
Great.
走吧
Then let's go.
对了 我喜欢你的夹克
Love that jacket on you, by the way.
谢谢
Thanks.
事实上
Actually…
我从里到外都是崭新的
The whole outfit is new.
（胡萨托尼克河 马萨诸塞州 36小时之前）
温彻斯特兄弟
Dean and Sammy winchester.
我们多久没见了
So, how long has it been?
六年级的夏天后就没见了
The summer before 6th grade.
我想起来了
Mm-hmm. I remember.
你给自己列了个书单
You assigned yourself your own reading list.
的确有那么回事 我差点忘了
That's right. I forgot about that.
你妈妈是我们遇到的最好的保姆
Your mom happens to be the best babysitter we ever had.
那时我还在洲际公路边上的
Well, when I was a maid at the mayflower,
五月花饭店做服务生
Out on the interstate …
连要孩子的想法都还没有
Long before you were even an idea …
他们的父亲从镇上经过
Their daddy used to pass through town.
把这对孩子交给了我照顾
And leave the boys with me.
然后自己就去 工作
While… he went off to…work.
有一次 他去了两个礼拜没回来
One time, he was gone for two weeks.
两个礼拜
Two weeks?
他经常一瘸一拐地回来
Oh, he'd always come limping back.
他爱着你们 孩子
He loved you boys.
你知道他都是在忙什么吗
Did you know what he did all that time?
小萨姆总是试图告诉我
Little sammy kept trying to tell me.
当然啦 我没相信他说的
Of course, I didn't believe him.
至少最开始是这样
Not at first, anyway.
凯蒂 我们的父亲
Katie, our dad, um…
碰巧是个驱魔专家
Happened to be an expert at getting rid of ghosts.
现在我们也是了
And now, so are we.
亲爱的 这就是我叫他们来的原因
That's why I called them, sweetie.
他们能帮我们
They can help us.
看来你们碰到了个皮皮鬼
Sounds like you guys got yourself a poltergeist.
是从我们住进来一两个月之后开始的
Started a month or two after we moved in.
一开始只是些碰撞声和敲击声
Yeah, first I-it was, uh, just bumps and knocks.
还有抓墙的声音
And, uh, scratches on the walls.
接着它开始弄坏东西
And then it started breaking things.
后来它就袭击了凯蒂
And then it attacked Katie?
那是两天前的事
That was two nights ago.
宝贝 他们看看吧
Can you show them, honey?
「殁童」
"Murdered Chylde"
凯蒂
Katie…
会好起来的
Everything's gonna be fine.
我保证
I promise.
你们何不出去渡个假
Why don't you guys take yourselves a little vacation,
这里我们来处理
And, uh, we'll take care of it.
谢谢
Thank you.
双层培根汉堡 大份油煎辣奶酪
Uh, bacon burger turbo, large chili-cheese fry,
一杯健康沙拉摇摇乐
Uh, and a health quake salad shake?
我知道 我知道
I know. I know.
这可不是我点的
It's, uh it's not mine.
尽情摇吧 小可爱
Oh, you shake it up, baby.
你知道吗 先不提皮皮鬼
You know, poltergeist aside,
唐娜看起来美极了 你说呢
Donna looked pretty good, don't you think?
老兄 你别说
Dude, don't tell me.
你还在对我们的保姆有性趣
you've still got the hots for our babysitter.
什么 怎么可能
What? No.
真奇怪
That's weird.
我只是觉得她 你知道
I'm just saying that she, you know, she …
她很能干
She's … she's doing good.
无论是对她的丈夫 还是对她的孩子
You know, with her husband, her kid.
所有那些恐怖的事情
This whole amityville thing.
困扰着他们 表现得很勇敢
being thrown at them, and they're hanging tough.
没错
Yeah.
你是否想过你也愿意过上像那样的生活呢
You ever think that you'd want something like that?
老婆 孩子 看看《整九码》（喜剧）
Wife, rugrats, the whole nine?
不 这些不会再属于我了
No. I mean, not really my thing anymore.
的确
Yeah.
你查到什么了
What do you got?
他们的房子
Uh, well, that house of theirs,
是栋老宅 非常老
It's old … really old.
几百年了
Um, hundreds of years.
并且我查到了一个传说
And I found a legend.
未被证实 但是还是
It's unconfirmed, but still…
怎么说的
Saying?
据称 在十八世纪二十年代
Supposedly, In the 1720s,
房子的拥有者叫以赛亚·皮克特
House was owned by a guy named Isaiah Pickett.
传说记载
Legend has it.
他施巫术把一个女人吊死在了后院
He hung a woman in his backyard for witchcraft …
一个叫玛吉·布里格斯的女人
A woman named Maggie Briggs.
那么说是个凶灵了
Okay, so an angry ghost witch?
就算那是真的
If it's true.
依然解释不了「殁童」的含义
That still doesn't explain what "Murderd Chylde" Means.
- 是的 - 或者那婊子被埋在哪儿
- No. - Or where the bitch is buried.
我的意思是说虽然路途遥远
You know, I mean, it's a long way back,
但是我可以试试
but I can see if I can find.
能否在小镇的历史记录中找到些什么
something in the town records.
值得一试
It's worth a shot.
有收获吗
So, any luck?
一点都没有
Bubkes.
连一个能证明
Can't even find proof a woman.
曾有人叫玛吉的证据都没找到
named Maggie briggs existed,
更别说她被埋在哪了
much less where she was planted.
好吧 咱们至少能在这里喘口气了
Okay. Well, we've got a minute to breathe here.
先处理一下眼前的事情吧
Let's pick it up first thing.
好的 回见
You bet. See you in a few.
是…
What…
谁…
Who…
我是柯林斯 在30号公路上
Yeah, this is Collins out on route 30.
我想我们找到他了
I think we got him.
弗兰克尔先生吗
Mr. Frankel?
你是加里·弗兰克尔先生吗
Mr. Gary Frankel?
谁
Who?
你的家人都急死了 孩子
Your family's worried sick about you, son.
我的…我的家人
My … my family?
我…哥哥打电话给你吗
My…brother called you?
来吧 先上车 别冻着
Come on. Get in before you freeze solid.
谢谢
Thanks, uh…
但是 我 我们在哪？
But, uh, w-where are we?
到家了 孩子
You're home, son.
不不 长官 我不住这里
N-no, officer, I-I'm not staying here.
加里 上帝啊
Gary! Oh, my god!
加里 谢天谢地 加里
Gary! Oh, god! Gary!
你还好吗
Are you all right?
哦 好的 好的
Oh! Okay. Okay. Okay.
抱歉 抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
这…这是怎么回事
Uh… w-what's going on here?
- 你什么意思 - 女士 你是谁啊
- What do you mean? - Lady, who are you?
年轻人 你喝醉了吗
Young man are you drunk?
你又是谁
And who are you?
加里 你喝醉了吗
Gary, are you drunk?
回答你父亲
Answer your father.
我爸
My father?
我
Look, I …
这是谁
Who is that?!
这他妈的是谁
Who the hell is that?!
他神志不清了
He's out of his gourd.
年轻人 你真让我惊讶
Young man, I'm very surprised at you.
是吗
Yeah.
我也同样惊讶啊
Tell me about it.
哦 太酷了
Oh, yeah.
好有男人味
Bring it!
他娘的
Holy crap.
萨姆
Sam.
哥们儿 你跑哪去了
Where the hell you been, man?
我都给你打了几个小时的电话了
I've been trying to call you for hours.
我去买了点东西
I picked up some food.
双层培根汉堡
Bacon burger turbo,
大份油煎辣奶酪 没错吧
large chili-cheese fry, right?
抱歉 兄弟 真的
Sorry, man. Really.
我 我只是没注意时间
I-I just … I lost track of time.
我不是成心让你生气的
I didn't mean to freak you out.
谢谢
Thanks.
不知道你干嘛用了那么久 但还是谢了
Don't know why it took you two hours, but thanks.
你没准会想去外面路上吃
Oh, you're gonna want to eat that on the road.
为什么
Why?
刚刚女佣进来 看见了这堆东西
The maid came in, saw that,
现在她们都被吓得够呛
and now they're all kind of freaking out.
你怎么会让女佣进来
Why'd you let the maid in?
她就这么进来了啊
It just happened.
随便吧
Whatever.
我去上个厕所 然后我们出发
I got to hit the head, and then we'll take off.
好 我在外面等你
All right. I-I'll be outside.
能出发了吗
Hey. You ready?
当然
Absolutely.
能让我开吗
Hey, can I drive?
太赞了
Oh, this is so sweet!
快点开行吗 安德瑞蒂（赛车选手）
You want to get the lead out, andretti? Come on.
现在是倒档
Reverse.
挂着倒档呢
Reverse!
还挂在倒档呢
It's in reverse.
我真的真的很抱歉
I am really, really sorry.
闭嘴
Shut up.
我是迪恩 这是我第N个号码
This is Dean's other other cell,
知道怎么做了吧
so you must know what to do.
迪恩 我把咱俩的手机都了个遍
Dean, I've called every phone we got.
兄弟 你在哪儿啊
Where are you, man?
那么
So…
这听上去真的挺疯狂
This is gonna sound crazy …
是很疯狂 不过
really crazy … but, um…
我觉得这身体不是我自己的
I think I'm in the wrong body.
需要你帮帮忙
Could use a little help here.
我好像还有 哮喘
I-I think I got asthma.
给我回个电话
Call me back.
幸运星汽车旅馆
Lucky Star Motel.
你好 能帮我连线102房间吗
Hello, could you please connect me to the room 102?
102房间吗
Room 102?
兄弟 他们午夜就退房了
Nah, man, those guys checked out middle of the night.
等等 「他们」 不止一个人吗
Wait … "Guys"? Plural?
是啊 一个穿皮革外套
Yeah … one leather jacket,
一个高得跟野人一样
one Sasquatch.
他们走了
They left.
你到底什么人啊
Who are you?
小孩挺聪明
Smart kid.
还是个处男
Virgin.
欲求不满的处男
Frustrated virgin.
巫术啊 加里
Witchcraft, huh, Gary?
你个邪恶的小混蛋
You little satanic bastard.
加里 吃早饭啦
Gary! Breakfast!
少来烦我
Leave me alone.
加里
Gary!
知道啦 来啦
All right, I'm coming!
加里 说说昨晚怎么回事吧
So, Gary, I'd like to know what happened last night.
相信我 我还想知道呢
So would I. Believe me.
我是说 你忘了自己的计划了么
I mean, what happened with the plan, buddy?
计划
The plan?
计划包括 高考啊 麻省理工啊
S.A.T.S, M.I.T. … The plan.
你想当工程师 你就得拿到全额奖学金
You want to be an engineer, you need a full ride.
你说说 花天酒地对你的计划有帮助么
So, tell me, how does getting drunk fit with the plan?
对
Right, yeah.
听着 伙计 恕我直言
Listen, buddy, no offense,
不过现在来讲
but at the moment,
我对你那什么计划一点兴趣都没有
I could give a rat's ass about your plan.
你说什么
Excuse me?
那个 我最近是不是有点 喜怒无常
Listen, h-have I seemed, uh, moody lately?
沉默寡言
Withdrawn?
而且对超自然的事着迷
Any … any occult fixations?
什么
What?
我猜猜 我的拉丁语超级赞
Let me guess … I'm amazing at Latin.
你确实很有语言天赋
You have an ear for languages.
最近邻居有没有丢宠物的
Um, any of the neighborhood pets go missing recently?
你嗑药了是吗
Are you smoking drugs?
莱纳德 他才没嗑药
Leonard. He is not smoking drugs.
你们有没有见过我看一本书
Have any of you seen me w-w-with a book?
很大 很古老 皮质封面
It'd be big and old, uh, leather-bound,
上面也许还有奇奇怪怪的字
maybe some strange writing on it.
或者坦白说 我不想让你们看见
Or frankly, I'm probably hiding it.
加里 不要
Gary, no!
怎么了
W-what?
你对小麦蛋白过敏
You're allergic to wheat gluten.
谷蛋白
Gluten.
- 你可露出马脚了 - 什么
- You've seriously sprung a leak. - What?
要是爸妈看见你那些又古老又诡异的书
If mom and dad ever found that creepy old book of yours,
那够你被禁足10年的
You'd be grounded for a decade.
可你竟敢在早餐的时候提起这事儿
And you're bringing it up at breakfast?
这么说确实有本书了
So there is a book.
雪梨 我把书藏哪儿了
Sydney, where do I keep it?
我们到底要去哪儿呢
So, uh, where we going, anyway?
去工作
To work.
那个案子
The case?
噢对 案件 当然了
Oh, right. Yeah … the case. Of course.
你想从哪儿开始着手呢
Where, uh, do you want to start?
既然你查不到玛吉·布里格斯埋在哪儿了
Well, since you couldn't find where Maggie Briggs was buried,
现在我们得来个墓地一日游
Now we have to do an all-day tombstone roll.
看能不能把她挖出来
to see if we can dig her up.
等等 是玛…玛吉·布里格斯吗
Wait. M-maggie Briggs?
你是说那个女巫玛吉·布里格斯吗
You mean, like … like, the witch Maggie Briggs?
是啊 福尔摩斯
Yeah, Sherlock.
她在地下室
Yeah, she's in the basement.
你说什么 什么地下室
Come again? W-what basement?
在以赛亚·皮克特的房子
Isaiah pickett's house.
传言是他绞死了她 但其实不然
Okay, there's this legend that he hung her, but he didn't.
真相是
The real truth is.
她怀了他的私生子
is that she was carrying his illegitimate child,
他杀了她然后把她埋在地下室里
and he killed her and then buried her in the basement.
她的「殁童」
Her "Murderd Chylde."
所以才会有那些刮痕
That would explain the scratches.
你怎么会知道这些
How do you know all this?
我可是做尽了无数的研究
Oh, I've done all kinds of research on it.
我是说 昨天晚上做的
I mean, you know… last night.
哦
Yeah.
干的不错啊
Nice work…I guess.
兄弟 打开啊
Aw, man, turn it up!
真的吗
Seriously?
废话
Hell yeah!
迪恩 有人盗用了我的身体
Dean! Someone has stolen my body!
你边上的家伙不是我
The guy right next to you is not me!
他妈的快查留言 操
Check your friggin' voicemail. Damn it.
加里
Gary?
你还好吧
Are you okay?
嗯 我是加里
Yeah, I'm Gary. Uh…
加里很好
Gary's okay.
我们什么时候开始用
So we're referring to ourselves.
第三人称称呼自己了啊
in the third person now?
我们听说了昨晚的事 怎么回事
We heard about last night. What happened?
喝醉了 没什么大不了
Got drunk. No big thing.
对了 我储物柜几号
Look, uh, what's my locker number?
什么 你酒还没醒吗
What? Are you … are you still drunk?
是啊 我看见你变成三个了
Yeah. Yeah. I see, like, three of you right now.
那个 我储物柜是几号
Um, so … so, what's my locker number?
哦 不 加里
Oh, no, Gary.
这本书可是相当糟糕
This is a very, very bad book.
大师在此 小婊子
Master chief is in the house, bizatches!
你还好吗
Are you all right?
嗯 没事
Yeah. Fine.
真他妈的见鬼
Well, I'll be damned.
柳苔
Willow moss.
啊 是啊
Yeah, right.
应该覆满女巫的坟墓吧
It's, uh, supposed to grow over witches' graves, right?
对啊
Yeah.
听着兄弟 我真的很抱歉
Hey, man, I'm really sorry about this.
什么东西
Sorry about what?
萨姆
Sam?!
你没事吧
You okay?
我们快他妈的离开这儿
Let's get the hell out of here!
哇哇哇 我们还得
Whoa, whoa, whoa. We still got to.
烧掉尸体 你这蠢材
burn the body, you idiot.
来
Come on.
伙计
Dude…
那一下真是太爽了
That was sweet!
嗨 加里 等等
Hey, gary, wait up!
你去哪儿
Where are you going?
有事
I got something to do.
你要逃课吗你
You're skipping class? You?
我只是
I'm just…
身体不舒服 行了吧
not feeling like myself, okay?
好吧 无论是什么
Well, whatever it is,
我们一起谈谈 兄弟 一起吧
we can talk it out, bro. Come with us.
我没时间 得走了 抱歉
I don't have time. I got to go. I'm sorry.
特雷弗
Trevor!
好吧 我还能怎么办
Well, what else was I supposed to do?
这是你们的
Here you go, guys.
帮个忙 甜心
Do me a favor, sweetheart.
能给我来个
Could you bring me a.
加量培根的芝士堡吗
cheeseburger with extra bacon?
上面再加个煎蛋 好吗
And fry an egg on top of it, would you?
没问题
Absolutely.
喔 听起来很棒嘛 我也要
Ooh, that … that sounds good. Ditto.
马上送到
Be right back with your order.
好吧 你到底是谁 你对萨姆做了什么
Okay, who are you and what have you done with sam?
你是什么意思
W-what do you mean?
现在又变成培根芝士堡了吗
Bacon cheeseburgers now?
我不知道 我难道不能吃吗
I don't know. I eat them, don't I?
不管怎么说 我们可在庆祝啊
Anyways, we are celebrating.
是的 我猜
Yeah, I guess.
没有白费劲 今天好样的
No one bites the dust. Nice work today.
你也是
You too.
我今天感觉真棒 兄弟 说真的
I had a, uh, really awesome day, man. Seriously.
爽
Sweet.
你觉得今天很棒吗
A really awesome day?
没错啊 难道不是吗
Yeah. Why not?
这次猎捕根本毫无章法 糟糕透顶
It was a random, d-list ghost hunt.
能算得上很棒吗
That's… that's awesome to you?
难道我就不能心情很好吗
I can't be in a good mood?
不 我想你应该不好 只是
Yeah, I guess. It's…
是的 完全可以心情好
No, actually.
不过这不像是你的作风 萨姆
It's not really your style, sam.
是吗 那么 就当我脱胎换骨了吧
Well, then, it's a new me.
行了 我为什么不该高兴点儿呢
I mean, come on. Why shouldn't I be happy?
我有枪 现在还能喝酒
I've got a gun, I'm getting drunk,
而且我还非常喜欢目前的样子
and I look like this.
我不清楚
I don't know.
你大概无法理解未来完全不由你做主的感觉
You ever feel like your whole future is being decided for you?
不 萨姆 我完全能理解
Uh, yeah, Sam, I feel like that a lot.
无论你这么反抗 都无法阻止计划发展
No matter how much you fight it, you can't stop the plan.
而且还是非常非常愚蠢的计划
The stupid, stupid plan.
所以 我弄不清楚
So, I don't know.
我就当它 不过是一时兴起
I guess it's, uh, it's just nice.
换个够炫的口味 仅此而已
to do a little ass-kicking for a change, that's all.
知道吗 我是喝醉了在说胡话
Uh, you know what? I … I'm drunk.
抱歉 当没听过
Sorry. Just … just forget it.
当然 没关系的
No, no. It's all right.
只是
It's, uh…
我举双手赞成你说的
I'll drink to that.
瞧瞧 我究竟是一个人喝醉了
Wow, you know, is it just me,
还是咱哥俩真一起在喝酒呢
or are we actually drinking together?
我们不经常这样吗
We don't do it that often, huh?
是啊 可以这么说
Yeah, you could say that.
我们就该多出来喝喝
Well, we should.
你可真好 迪恩
You're a good guy, Dean.
老弟 你可真喝醉了
Man, you are drunk.
吃的来了
Here we go.
- 谢谢 - 慢慢享用
- Thank you. - Enjoy.
是有点儿 但我说真的
No, but I mean it.
你真是个好人
You really are a good guy.
真赞
The bread alone!
顺便一提 相当中意你身上这件夹克噢
Love that jacket on you, by the way.
谢谢夸奖
Thanks.
实际上
Actually…
这身行头里里外外都是新的哦
The whole outfit is new.
我们要去那啥了
We're gonna do it!
这他妈的搞毛啊
What the hell's going on?!
你想叫就叫啊
You can scream all you want.
叫破嗓子也没人理你 我父母都出城了
No one can hear you! My parents are out of town!
加里
Gary.
小特 怎么啦
T. What up?
你人在哪儿呢
Where are you?
现在无法告诉你
Uh, I can't really tell you right now,
不过 哥们 你绝对不会相信的
but, man, you wouldn't believe it.
好吧 那么 迪恩在哪儿
Well… well, where's Dean?
6号公路旁的四叶草旅店 干嘛问这个
Uh, the cloverleaf on route 6. Why?
搞什么 你还没杀了他吗
You mean you haven't killed him yet?
什么 等等 等一下 你说什么呢
What? Wait, wait, wait, wait. W-what do you mean?
你们要杀了迪恩
Kill Dean?
我 正在计划中
I'm…building up to it.
听着 加里 我们这边有点儿麻烦
Look, Gary, we got problems here.
比如说
For one…
我此刻眼前就立着你的躯体
I'm looking at your body right now …
而里面却是另一个家伙
with this other dude in it.
- 什么 - 真的 他已经去过你家
- What? - Yeah, he's been in your house.
还跟你父母打过照面
He's hanging out with your parents.
好了 先冷静一下
Okay, just…calm down.
无论他说什么 都没人相信他吧
Whatever he says, no one's gonna believe him, right?
如此看来 一切都在掌控之中
I mean, w-we're still good.
拜托你快动手杀了那混账家伙吧
Just hurry up and kill the son of a bitch already, would you?
别催我 我自有分寸
Don't rush me. I'll do it.
好吧 你好自为之
Yeah, you better.
先挂了噢
Uh…got to go.
老天 这有点儿超出我想象了
Oh, man. I am in way over my head.
我看他八成搞不定
I don't think he's gonna do it.
别紧张 我们说得可是加里
Just relax. This is Gary we're talking about.
这该死的究竟是怎么回事
What the hell is going on here?
你们这么会知道迪恩的
How do you know who Dean is?
大家都知道迪恩
Everybody knows Dean.
他可是地狱的头号红人
He's "Hell's most wanted."
噢 不是吧
Oh, no.
不会吧
No.
你们这些蠢货和恶魔对话了吗
Have you idiots been talking to demons?
是的 没错 的确如此
Oh, right. We're the idiots.
你们还是孩子
You're just kids.
你们根本不清楚自己在搞些什么
You have no idea what you're messing with.
我们知道迪恩的脑袋价值不菲
Well, we know that there's a price on Dean's head,
所以我们是来取其性命的
And we're the ones that are gonna collect.
这到底是怎么回事
What's that supposed to mean?
大约一个月之前 我们来到这里
About a month ago, we were down here …
- 诺拉 - 干什么 我们不能说吗
- Nora. What? - We're not allowed to talk about him?
我们来到这里 拿着那本书玩玩
We were down here, goofing around with that book.
我当时的确没有向暗黑之王祷告
Um, I wouldn't exactly call praying to our dark overlord.
只是「玩玩」而已
"Goofing around."
别打断我 特雷弗
Don't be a loser, Trev.
别搅和 特雷弗
Yeah, Trev.
然后 突然间 灯光忽闪忽灭
Anyway, all of a sudden, the lights flickered.
紧接着加里进入了一种怪异的状态
And Gary went into this weird trance.
他紧闭双眼 拿起铅笔 画出了这个
He closed his eyes, picked up a pencil, and drew this.
你知道这事为什么怪异吗
And you know what's really weird?
加里根本不会画画
Gary can't draw.
他说听到头脑里有个声音告诉他
He said he heard a voice in his head.
恶魔正在悬赏追杀这个画上的家伙
The demons were putting out a bounty on this guy.
悬赏
A bounty?
面向全国的女巫
Yeah, to, like, every witch or satanist.
或者魔教徒
Across the whole country.
而加里 他要做的就是找到你
But Gary … Gary's the one who spotted you.
像电影「辣妈辣妹」里那种换身份的把戏
And the "Freaky Friday" Crap?
那是书中的另一个咒语
Another spell from the book.
是加里的主意 就像特洛伊木马那样
Gary's idea … go in trojan horse-style.
他的确很聪明
He's really smart.
确实如此 要是他能说到做到就更好了
That is, if he has the bean bags to go through with it.
听我说
Listen to me.
你们犯了一个可怕的错误
You are making a terrible mistake.
我们现在说的是一场与恶魔的交易
We're talking about a demon deal …
杀掉一个人
Killing somebody.
这不是一场游戏
This isn't a game.
你们正在走向绝路
You're crossing a line you won't come back from.
相信我
Believe me.
干嘛
What?
没什么 我 我…
Nothing. I-I…
诺拉 别告诉我你真的相信这个蠢蛋
Nora, don't tell me you're actually listening to this jerk.
我不知道
I don't know.
或许
M-maybe.
我是说 或许他说的是对的
I-I mean, what if he has a point?
真不敢相信 先是加里动摇 然后是你
I don't believe this. First Gary, now you.
我就是不-
I can't …
你知道吗
You know what?
好吧
Fine.
你想把事情做完
You want something done right…
干嘛 你想怎样
What, you're gonna …
你要自己去杀了迪恩 是吗 猛男
You're gonna go kill Dean yourself, tough guy?
没这个必要
Don't have to.
我可以靠这个
I can do this.
不 别开玩笑了
N-no. Y-you can't be serious.
我可以从那些恶魔里叫一个过来
I'm calling up one of these bad boys,
摆平这一切 然后坐享其成
Turning these punks over, and getting paid.
钞票 钞票 爽歪了
Dolla, dolla bills, y'all!
我认为这绝不是个好主意
I-I really don't think that that's a good idea.
绝对不是
It's not.
- 这个主意糟透了 - 没人问你的意见
- It's a very, very bad idea. - No one asked you.
你不是萨姆
You're not Sam.
你他妈的是谁
Who the hell are you?
别这样做 我求你了
Don't do this. I'm begging you.
特雷弗 我觉得他说的没错
Trevor, I think he's right.
你还想上瓦萨大学呢 不是吗
Hey, you want to get into Vassar, don't you?
求你了 停下
Please! Stop!
[咒语]
你会把我们都害死的
You're gonna get us all killed!
[咒语]
难道我念错咒语了
Maybe I said it wrong.
诺拉
Nora?
别 别碰她
No! No, no! Don't touch her!
诺拉 你还好吗
Nora, you okay?
好极了
Oh, yeah.
我感觉棒极了
I'm peachy.
那么 你叫我出来干嘛 小淘气
So, what'd you call me here for, skippy?
除非是…
Unless…
到晚餐时间了吗
It's dinnertime?
什么 我 不是-
What? I-I … n-no.
我们找到迪恩·温彻斯特了
Uh, we have Dean Winchester.
你找到了
You do?
在哪
Where?
特雷弗 闭紧你的嘴
Trevor, keep your mouth shut.
在六号公路的四叶草旅店
The cloverleaf motel over on route 6.
萨姆
Sam?
是你在那里吗
Is that you in there?
你不是一个98磅重的傻子吗
Well, aren't you just 98 pounds of nothing.
那个孩子是个白痴
The kid is a moron.
他不知道迪恩在哪里
He doesn't have any idea where Dean is.
所以 若是山姆在这个身体里面
So, if Sam's in this body,
那谁在山姆的身体里面
Who's in Sam's?
是一个危险的巫师
A dangerous warlock.
叫加里
Named Gary.
你是说你找到了迪恩·温彻斯特
You mean to tell me you've got Dean Winchester.
和萨姆·温彻斯特的肉身吗
and Sam Winchester's meat suit?
一个空空的皮囊 等着有人来接管
An empty vessel just waiting to be filled.
你是要把这两个人都献给我吗
And you're handing them both over to me?
是 我想是吧
Uh, y-yeah. I guess.
那么
Well…
我要祝贺你
I got to hand it to you.
我真是深受感动
I'm impressed.
谢谢
Thanks.
我冒昧的问一句
So, if you don't mind my asking…
有报酬吗
There's a reward?
当然有
Sure.
我对你表示无尽感激
My…undying gratitude.
什么 你当真
What, are you serious?
安静点 你个傻瓜
Be quiet, you idiot!
暗自庆信吧 小鬼
Consider yourself lucky, kid.
等一下
Uh, w-wait a minute!
我们在这里累死累活
We worked our asses off here,
我要我的报酬
And, uh, I want my reward!
好吗
Please?
好的
Okay.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你是对的
You're right.
我可以给你什么呢
What can I get you?
100万美元怎么样
Well, h-how about a million bucks?
天哪 特雷弗 闭嘴快跑
Oh, for god's sake, Trevor, just shut up and run!
现在100万可不值钱了
A million doesn't buy you much these days.
1000万怎么样
Why not make it 10?
好的 那就1000万
Okay, $10 mill.
我还想
And I want…
让明蒂·施瓦兹爱上我
…I want Mindy Schwartz to fall in love with me.
爱情 金钱
Love…money.
人类最基本的需求
Sticking to the basics.
我理解
I can respect that.
但这是我付报酬的方式
But here's my counter.
嗯
Yep.
尝起来是像白痴
Tastes like moron.
你有38条留言
You have 38 messages.
这听起来很疯狂
This is gonna sound crazy …
真是疯狂 但是我觉得我上错身了
really crazy … but, um, I think I'm in the wrong body.
迪恩 你边上的家伙不是我
Dean, the guy right next to you is not me!
迪恩 他妈的快查留言 操
Dean, check your friggin' voicemail. Damn it.
好了 老兄
All right, pal.
你快老实交代 不然我可动私刑了
Either you start talking or I start waterboarding.
老天爷 别伤害我
Oh, my god. Please, don't hurt me.
求你了 我很抱歉 真的很抱歉
Please! I'm sorry! I'm so, so sorry!
好吧 别装死 装逼男
Okay. Hey, pull it together, champ.
我可不想死 真的不想死
I don't want to die. I don't want to die.
萨姆在哪里
Where's Sam?
在我朋友的地窖里
In my … my friend's basement.
他的父母离开镇上了
His parents are out of town.
父母
Parents?
你多大了
How old are you?
17岁
17.
17岁啊
17?
诺拉
Nora?
现在可不是
Not at the moment.
真见鬼
Damn it!
小可爱 今晚该给你点儿小奖励
Boy, you earned your dessert tonight, kiddo.
告诉我 你想要什么
Tell me … what is it you want?
我都可以满足你
Anything.
什么都可以吗
Anything?
尽管提吧
Lay it on me.
我想成为一位巫师
I want to be a witch.
真正的巫师
For real.
非常强大的巫师
And really powerful.
选得好
Mm. Good choice.
我明白了
I get it.
再也不会有老爸烦着你考什么麻省理工
No daddy, no M.I.T.
也没有人再为你设定好未来
No plan.
你将变得高大而强壮
You get to be big and strong,
别人再也不能对你指手画脚
And no one can tell you what to do anymore.
但先得有个小小的礼节程序
There's just one small formality first.
你得见见我们的老大
You got to meet the boss.
老大
The boss?
你知道啊 伟大的撒旦陛下
You know … your satanic majesty,
当今的小孩子对他还有很多其他称呼呢
or whatever the kids are calling it these days.
那个魔鬼吗
The devil?
不
Uh…no.
那个
O-okay.
不用了吧
It's okay.
我真的不想惊动他
I…don't really want to bother him.
但他想见见你
Oh, but he's gonna want to meet you.
放轻松
Relax.
没事的
It'll be easy.
他只是问你个小小的问题
He's just gonna ask you one little question,
你只要回答「是」就可以
and all you got to do is say "Yes."
之后呢 你就能得到你想要的
And then… you get your reward.
[咒语]
那算什么
What was that?
没什么
Uh, n-nothing.
你是想驱逐我吗
Were you trying to exorcise me?!
你这臭小鬼
You little piece of crap?!
[咒语]
Adios 拜拜了 贱人
Adios, bitch!
呃 应该是Audi nos
Uh, it's "Audi nos."
[咒语]
正常了吧
So, we good?
终于正常了
Yeah. We're good.
老兄 回归真身的感觉真好
Oh, man, it's nice to be back.
是啊 很爽
Yeah. Awesome.
这个
So…
加里啊
Gary…
我知道 是我不好
Yeah. I know … my bad.
「是我不好」
"My bad"?
小鬼 这样轻描淡写可不成
Kid, "My bad" ain't gonna cut it.
要知道 如果你是成年人
See, if you were of voting age…
你就死定了
You'd be dead.
因为我们会宰了你
Because we would kill you.
除非你老老实实的再也不碰这些
So either you straighten up and fly right.
不然我们非宰了你不可
or we will kill you.
明白了吗
Are we clear?
- 一清二楚 - 这还差不多
- Crystal. - Good.
真讨厌
Crap.
听着 加里
Gary, look.
听听过来人的建议
Take it from someone who knows …
别气馁啊 伙计
Chin up, man.
你的生活其实并没有很糟
Your life ain't that bad.
你见过我父母了吗
Uh, you met my parents.
是啊 那又怎样 这是你的生活
Yeah. So what? It's your life.
你不喜欢他们对你指手画脚 就说出来
You don't like their plan for you, tell them to cram it.
反抗一下
Rebel a little bit.
当然 用正常的方式 不要搞邪门歪道
In a healthy, non-satanic way, of course.
顺便 你知道诺拉为何喜欢巫术吗
By the way, you know why Nora's into witchcraft?
什么意思
What do you mean?
她不是喜欢撒旦
She doesn't like satan,
你这笨蛋 她喜欢的是你
you moron. She likes you.
真的吗
Really?
你这样觉得吗
You … you think?
对 我能看出来
Ah. I know.
我告诉你 小子
I'm telling you, kid …
我真希望自己是你
I wish I had your life.
真的吗
You do?
多谢
Thanks.
快走吧
Get out of here.
你真是体贴啊
That was a nice thing to say.
我根本是在撒谎
I totally lied.
那孩子的生活烂透了
That kid's life sucked ass.
那些苹果派和家人的唠叨 超压抑
All that apple-pie, family crap? It's stressful.
信我没错 我们才不会想要那种生活
Trust me … we didn't miss a damn thing.
或许我们根本不了解那种生活吧
Or we don't know what we're missing.
拜托 老哥 小点声
Hey, come on, man. Turn it down.
欢迎归来 《科特》（儿童情景喜剧）
Welcome back, Kotter.